[
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the Super Mario series, the character Pauline is a Princess like Princess Peach.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language 'Simlish' was The Sims (2000).",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "There is an island in Japan called \u014ckunoshima, A.K.A. 'Rabbit Island', so named because of it's huge population of rabbits.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Politics",
        "question": "Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman's birthday while he was president.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "'Ananas' is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Books",
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Hermione destroyed the fourth Horcrux by stabbing it with the Sword of Gryffindor.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]